Guide to the Laura Foreman Papers 1949-2001 MSS.122
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Video recordings, 1973-1985; 41.25 Linear Feet 33 Paige Cartons
  - Subseries A: Original tapes
    - Bird House #4, undated; ID: 122.0153 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0153)
    - Bird House #5, undated; ID: 122.0154 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0154)
    - Bird House #6, undated; ID: 122.0155 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0155)
      Duration: Unkown
    - Bird House #7, undated; ID: 122.0156 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0156)
    - "Untitled" - NYSCA, 1979; ID: 122.0157 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0157)
      Alternate Title: Good Dub of NYSCA "Untitled"
    - AFI Work Tape, undated; ID: 122.0158 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0158)
    - AFI Work Dub (?), undated; ID: 122.0159 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0159)
    - Lothlorein, undated; ID: 122.0160 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0160)
      Alternate Title: Interviews - Becky & Jeff
    - Scratch Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0161 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0161)
      Alternate Title: Practice Editing Tape
    - Scratch Tape, undated; ID: 122.0162 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0162)
    - NYSCA Work Tape, 1978; ID: 122.0163 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0163)
    - Work Tape #1 - NYSCA, 1978; ID: 122.0164 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0164)
    - Davidson's Sound Tape, 1978; ID: 122.0165 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0165)
      Alternate Title: NYSCA "Untitled"
    - Laura's VO Audio Dub, 1978; ID: 122.0166 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0166)
    - Laura's Intro VO, 1978; ID: 122.0167 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0167)
      Duration: 5 minutes
    - Assemblage Tape - NYSCA, 1978; ID: 122.0168 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0168)
    - In-House Dub of NYSCA Tape, 1978; ID: 122.0169 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0169)
    - Tape #7 - Dub, 1980; ID: 122.0170 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0170)
    - Tape #7 - New Work Dub, 1980; ID: 122.0171 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0171)
      Alternate Title: Laura Talking to Mirror
    - Tape #8 - New Dub, 1980; ID: 122.0172 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0172)
    - Tape #8 - Dub, 1980; ID: 122.0173 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0173)
    - Tape #9 and #10 - Dub Tape, 1980; ID: 122.0174 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0174)
    - Untitled, CH. 13 - Dub #1, undated; ID: 122.0175 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0175)
    - Untitled, CH. 13 - Dub #2, undated; ID: 122.0176 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0176)
    - Tapes #9 and #10 - New Dubs, 1980; ID: 122.0177 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0177)
    - Nick Yanni's Tomorrow's Television Tonight, 1979; ID: 122.0178 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0178)
    - Colorized B & W - Tape #2, undated; ID: 122.0179 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0179)
    - New Master Original, undated; ID: 122.0180 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0180)
    - CH 13 Guggenheim - Dub, undated; ID: 122.0181 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0181)
    - Untitled, 1979; ID: 122.0182 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0182)
      Alternate Title: Untitled; Rough Assemblage From Work In Progress
    - Scractch Tape #1, undated; ID: 122.0183 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0183)
    - a deux, 1977; ID: 122.0184 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0184)
      Duration: 9 minutes
    - a deux - NYSCA, 1978; ID: 122.0185 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0185)
      Alternate Title: a deux
    - Heirlooms; a deux, 1977; ID: 122.0186 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0186)
      Duration: 25 minutes
    - Songandance; Locrian, 1973; ID: 122.0187 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0187)
      Duration: 60 minutes
    - Fantasy / Teddy Bears, 1978; ID: 122.0188 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0188)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy Teddy Bear Shots
    - Fantasy / Dummies Reel #1, 1978; ID: 122.0189 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0189)
      Alternate Title: Dummies Reel #1
    - Fantasy / Dummies Reel #2, 1978; ID: 122.0190 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0190)
      Alternate Title: Dummies Reel #2
    - Fantasy / Prop Room Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0191 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0191)
      Duration: 20 minutes]
      Alternate Title: Tape #1 Laura in Prop Room
    - Fantasy / Prop Room Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0192 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0192)
      Alternate Title: Laura in Prop Room
    - Fantasy / Dressing Room at Japan House, 1978; ID: 122.0193 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0193)
      Alternate Title: Satoru at Japan House, the Marpetts #1
    - Fantasy / Laura Talking to Mirror Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0194 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0194)
      Alternate Title: Schtict Tape #1
    - Fantasy / Laura Talks to Mirror Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0195 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0195)
      Alternate Title: Schtict Tape #2
    - Fantasy / Laura Talking to Herself, 1978; ID: 122.0196 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0196)
      Alternate Title: Laura's Schtict Tape #3 & #4
    - Fantasy / Mirror Shots Tape I, 1978; ID: 122.0197 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0197)
      Alternate Title: Mirror Shots Tape I
    - FANTASY / Mirror Shots Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0198 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0198)
      Alternate Title: Mirror Tape II
    - Fantasy; Poster Tape 1, 1978; ID: 122.0199 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0199)
      Alternate Title: Poster Shots #1
    - Poster Tape 2, 1978; ID: 122.0200 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0200)
      Currently unavailable until duplicatio occurs.
      Alternate Title: Poster Tape #2
    - 19th St. Shot, 1978; ID: 122.0201 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0201)
    - 19th St., 1978; ID: 122.0202 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0202)
      Alternate Title: 19th Street Front Steps and Upstairs
    - Fantasy - Japan House I, 1978; ID: 122.0203 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0203)
      Alternate Title: Japan House Reel I
    - Japan House 2, 1978; ID: 122.0204 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0204)
      Alternate Title: Japan House Reel II
    - Japan House III & Barre Shots, 1978; ID: 122.0205 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0205)
      Alternate Title: Japan House Reel III and Fantasy Shots Tape 5
    - Barre Shots and Playground I, 1978; ID: 122.0206 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0206)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy - Playground Tape I
    - Playground II, 1978; ID: 122.0207 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0207)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy - Playground Tape II
    - Installation I, 1978; ID: 122.0208 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0208)
      Alternate Title: Installation #1
    - Installation 2 / Satoru's Loft, 1978; ID: 122.0209 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0209)
      Alternate Title: Installation #2
    - Installation / Poetry, 1978; ID: 122.0210 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0210)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy Shots of Laura Upstairs
    - Saturo at Bar Talking About His Life - Dub #1, 1978; ID: 122.0211 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0211)
      Orignal format: 1/2 in. Open Reel
    - Laura / Mirror, 1978; ID: 122.0212 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0212)
      Alternate Title: Japan House #2
    - Original Snow & Dances - Tape #2, undated; ID: 122.0213 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0213)
      Alternate Title: Roof Section - Applause and Close-up
    - Original Snow Shot, undated; ID: 122.0214 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0214)
    - Original Snow Shot #3, 1978; ID: 122.0215 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0215)
      Alternate Title: Snow Shot, Roof Section, Close-ups, Barre Section
    - Tape Recorder Shot, 1979; ID: 122.0216 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0216)
      Alternate Title: Recycle
    - Satoru Dancing Roof Section at Angle, undated; ID: 122.0217 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0217)
    - Documentary Edit & Snow Shot / Stephen Backer, undated; ID: 122.0218 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0218)
      Alternate Title: Laura Foreman Dance Theatre Documentary
    - Laura Foreman Interview, undated; ID: 122.0219 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0219)
      Alternate Title: LFDT Tape #1 Gertrude Stein Piece
    - Auditions (Women) & Laura at Loft, 1978; ID: 122.0220 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0220)
    - Auditions (Women's) #1, 1977; ID: 122.0221 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0221)
    - Men's Auditions #1, 1978; ID: 122.0222 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0222)
    - Men's Auditions #2, 1978; ID: 122.0223 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0223)
    - Male Auditions #3, 1978; ID: 122.0224 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0224)
    - LFDT Audition Callback Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0225 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0225)
    - LFDT Audition Callback Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0226 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0226)
    - Rehearsal #1, undated; ID: 122.0227 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0227)
    - Rehearsal #2 & Loft Lookover, 1978; ID: 122.0228 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0228)
    - Laura Loft looking, 1978; ID: 122.0229 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0229)
      Duration: 18 minutes
    - Annie in Office, 1978; ID: 122.0230 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0230)
    - Laura Looking at Lighting in Satoru's Loft / Luncheonette, 1978; ID: 122.0231 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0231)
    - Laura at Parsons #2, 1978; ID: 122.0232 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0232)
    - Laura at New School #1, 1978; ID: 122.0233 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0233)
    - Laura at Parsons #3 & Laura at New School #4, 1978; ID: 122.0234 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0234)
    - Ward-Nasse Gallery / John & Laura Doing NYSCA Application, 1978; ID: 122.0235 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0235)
    - Laura and John Doing NYSCA Application, 1978; ID: 122.0236 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0236)
    - Lecture Demonstration at Baruch College, 1978; ID: 122.0237 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0237)
    - Cathy Abbott and Barbara Buckner - Audition Tape, 1978; ID: 122.0238 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0238)
    - Manuel Carvalho Audition Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0239 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0239)
    - Manuel Carvalho Audition Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0240 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0240)
    - Mark Graff Audition Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0241 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0241)
      Alternate Title: John and Satoru Rehearsing Fragments and "UPS"
    - Mark Graff Audition Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0242 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0242)
      Alternate Title: John and Satoru rehearsing Fragments and "UPS"
    - Jeff Bush and Celia Ipiotis Audition, 1978; ID: 122.0243 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0243)
      Alternate Title: John and Satoru rehearsing "UPS"
    - Greg Tonning Audition Tape, 1978; ID: 122.0244 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0244)
    - Louis Jaffe Audition Tape, 1978; ID: 122.0245 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0245)
    - Satoru and Laura at Hoarty's Studio Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0246 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0246)
    - Laura at Hoarty's Studio Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0247 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0247)
    - Burlesque Tape, 1977; ID: 122.0248 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0248)
    - Laura Poetry Reading #1, 1978; ID: 122.0249 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0249)
    - Laura Poetry Reading #2, 1978; ID: 122.0250 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0250)
    - Franklin Furnace #1, 1978; ID: 122.0251 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0251)
    - Franklin Furnace #2, 1978; ID: 122.0252 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0252)
    - LFDT; NEA Grant Tape - Dub, 1978; ID: 122.0253 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0253)
      Alternate Title: "Heirlooms" & "a deux"
    - a deux; Cubiculo; Tape I Section II, 1977; ID: 122.0254 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0254)
    - a deux; Cubiculo; Tape II Section II, 1977; ID: 122.0255 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0255)
    - a deux; Cubiculo; Tape III Section III, 1977; ID: 122.0256 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0256)
    - a deux; Cubiculo; Tape IV, 1977; ID: 122.0257 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0257)
    - a deux #1, 1977; ID: 122.0258 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0258)
    - a deux #2, 1977; ID: 122.0259 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0259)
    - a deux #3, 1977; ID: 122.0260 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0260)
    - a deux #1, 1974; ID: 122.0261 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0261)
    - a deux #2 1974, ID: 122.0262 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0262)
    - Postludes and a deux; "Live" ATL, 1975; ID: 122.0263 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0263)
      Duration: 23 minutes
      Alternate Title: Postludes and a deux
    - Heirlooms - Original Edit, 1977; ID: 122.0264 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0264)
      Alternate Title: Heirlooms
    - Heirlooms Rehearsal #1, 1977; ID: 122.0265 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0265)
    - Heirlooms Rehearsal #2, 1977; ID: 122.0266 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0266)
    - Heirlooms Rehearsal #3, 1977; ID: 122.0267 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0267)
    - Heirlooms Rehearsal #4, 1977; ID: 122.0268 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0268)
    - Heirlooms - Costume Tape, 1977; ID: 122.0269 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0269)
    - Laura Foreman - #6, 1977; ID: 122.0270 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0270)
    - Laura Foreman - #7, 1977; ID: 122.0271 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0271)
    - Laura Foreman - #8, 1977; ID: 122.0272 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0272)
    - Heirlooms - Tape #9, 1977; ID: 122.0273 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0273)
    - Heirlooms - Tape #10, 1977; ID: 122.0274 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0274)
    - Heirlooms - Tape #7, 1977; ID: 122.0275 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0275)
    - Heirlooms - Section 1 with Lights, May 5, 1977; ID: 122.0276 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0276, Case 122.0276)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      DVD access copy available.
    - Heirlooms - 2nd Section with Lights, 1977; ID: 122.0277 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0277, Case 122.0277)
    - Heirlooms - 3rd Section with Lights, undated; ID: 122.0278 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0278, Case 122.0278)
    - Heirlooms - Section One, First Intermission, 1977; ID: 122.0279 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0279, Case 122.0279)
      Duration: 24 minutes
    - Heirlooms - Section Two - Straight, undated; ID: 122.0280 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0280, Case 122.0280)
    - Heirlooms - Section Three - Straight, 1977; ID: 122.0281 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0281, Case 122.0281)
    - Roxanne Talks Her Heirlooms Part - Tape 1, 1977; ID: 122.0282 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0282)
    - Roxanne Talks Her Heirlooms Part - Tape 2, undated; ID: 122.0283 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0283)
    - Satoru & Roxanne - Heirlooms, 1977; ID: 122.0284 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0284)
    - Roxanne's Part - Heirlooms, 1977; ID: 122.0285 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0285)
    - Heirlooms Act II - Satoru and Roxanne, 1977; ID: 122.0286 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0286)
    - Heirlooms - Additional Notes for Roxanne, 1977; ID: 122.0287 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0287)
    - Heirlooms Act III - Satoru & Roxanne, 1977; ID: 122.0288 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0288)
    - Laura's Part & Snapshots, 1977; ID: 122.0289 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0289)
    - Ward-Nasse "Program" #1, 1976; ID: 122.0290 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0290)
      Alternate Title: Program
    - Ward-Nasse "Program" #2, 1976; ID: 122.0291 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0291)
    - Program, 1976; ID: 122.0292 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0292)
    - Program #1, 1976; ID: 122.0293 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0293)
    - Program #2, 1976; ID: 122.0294 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0294)
    - Laura Foreman Interview, 1976; ID: 122.0295 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0295)
      Alternate Title: Interview For Dance, New York Style #17
    - Monopoly - Video I, 1976; ID: 122.0296 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0296)
      Alternate Title: Monopoly
    - Monopoly - Video II, 1976; ID: 122.0297 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0297)
    - Monopoly in Soho, 1976; ID: 122.0298 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0298)
    - City of Angels - Delacorte Theater / New York Dance Festival, 1975; ID: 122.0299 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0299)
      Duration: 17 minutes
      Alternate Title: City of Angels
    - City of Angels - Wollman Hall, 1975; ID: 122.0300 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0300)
    - City of Angels - "Live", 1975; ID: 122.0301 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0301)
    - City of Angels - Barnard College, 1974; ID: 122.0302 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0302)
    - City of Angels - Left Angled Audience View Version, 1975; ID: 122.0303 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0303)
    - City of Angels - Audience View Version, 1975; ID: 122.0304 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0304)
    - 1.Nancy's Part of City 2. Still Life, 1975; ID: 122.0305 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0305)
      Alternate Title: [1]-- City of Angels [2.]-- Songanddance
    - Spaces - MOMA, 1973-1974; ID: 122.0306 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0306)
    - Spaces - Edit Dub, 1973; ID: 122.0307 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0307)
    - Corrected version of Locrian / Spaces, 1975; ID: 122.0308 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0308)
    - Locrian version of Spaces at Moma, 1975; ID: 122.0309 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0309)
    - Locrian at ATL, 1973; ID: 122.0310 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0310)
      Alternate Title: Locrian
    - ATL Version of Locrian, 1975; ID: 122.0311 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0311)
    - Glass and Shadows - No Media, 1975; ID: 122.0312 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0312, Case 122.0312)
      Duration: 19 minutes
    - Glass and Shadows - With Media & Lighting, 1975; ID: 122.0313 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0313, Case 122.0313)
    - Glass and Shadows - Choreography Only (Copy), March 7, 1975; ID: 122.0314 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0314, Case 122.0314)
    - songandance #1, 1973; ID: 122.0315 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0315)
      Alternate Title: songandance
    - songandance #2, 1973; ID: 122.0316 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0316)
    - Signals, May 17, 1975; ID: 122.0317 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0317, Case 122.0317)
      Alternate Title: Signals
    - Signals - MOMA, 1973; ID: 122.0318 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0318)
    - postludes - at New School, 1974; ID: 122.0319 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0319)
      Alternate Title: postludes
    - 1. Fantasy / Poetry Installation 2. Poetry Reading #1 3. Poetry Reading #2, 1978; ID: 122.0320 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0320)
    - 1. Mug Shot Tape #1 2. Mug Shot Tape #2 3.Arp Room, 1978; ID: 122.0321 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0321)
    - 1. Arp Room #2 2. MF Arp Room Tape #1 3. MF Arp Room Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0322 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0322)
    - 1. MF Arp Room Tape #3 2. Enteries Tape #1 3. Enteries Tape #2 4. Enteries Tape #3, 1976-1978; ID: 122.0323 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0323)
    - 1. Enteries Tape #4 2. Enteries Tape #5 3. Enteries Tape #6, 1978; ID: 122.0324 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0324)
    - 1. Enteries Tape #7 2. Enteries Tape #8 3. Enteries Tape #9, 1978; ID: 122.0325 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0325)
    - 1. Enteries Tape #10 2. Enteries Tape #11 3. Enteries Tape #12, 1978; ID: 122.0326 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0326)
    - 1. Enteries Tape #12 - Last Take 2. Enteries Tape #13 3. Enteries Tape #14 4. Enteries Tape #15, 1978; ID: 122.0327 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0327)
    - 1. Enteries 16 Documentary 2. Enteries 17 Documentary 3. Enteries 18 Documentary, 1978; ID: 122.0328 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0328)
    - 1. Satoru Rehearsing 2. China's China 3. Laura Construction 4. Satoru Rehearsing, 1978; ID: 122.0329 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0329)
    - 1. Satoru Dancing 2. 6/28 Dance 3. Satoru on Floor, 1978; ID: 122.0330 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0330)
    - 1. Satoru on Floor, cont. 2. Wall dance 3. Satoru Rehearsing 4. Hound Dog, 1978; ID: 122.0331 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0331)
    - 1. Sarabande Rehearsal Tape 2. Go Rehearsal Tape 3. Go Movements Rehearsal Tape, 1978; ID: 122.0332 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0332)
    - 1. Hound Dog & 19th St. Shots 2. Satoru at Kitchen Tape #1 of 5 3. Rehearsal, 1978, undated; ID: 122.0333 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0333)
    - 1. Mark Fisher Audition tape 2. Jim Vito Audition Tape 3. Barbara Laurence/ Barbara Jousen Audition Tape, 1978; ID: 122.0334 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0334)
    - 1. Satoru Marking Out Sequences 2. Tripod Test Tape 3. Satoru Opening Gifts, 1978; ID: 122.0335 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0335)
    - 1. Satoru Upset & Laura's Response 2. Satoru Warming Up 3. Satoru at Barre, 1978; ID: 122.0336 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0336)
    - 1. Satoru at Barre, cont. 2. Satoru Talking About His Life 3. Mug Shots 4. Snow Shot Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0337 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0337)
    - 1. Snow Shot Tape #2 2. Snow Shot Tape #3 3. Snow Shot Tape #4, 1978; ID: 122.0338 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0338)
    - 1. Snow Shot Ruth Tape #1 2. Snow Shot Fred Tape #1 2. Snow Shot Buy Take 4. Snow Shot M. Fisher, 1978; ID: 122.0339 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0339)
    - 1. Satoru at Kitchen #1 2. Performance - Audience 3. Janice and Annie Setting Up, 1978; ID: 122.0340 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0340)
    - 1. Japan House #1 2. Japan House #2 3. Japan House #3, 1978; ID: 122.0341 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0341)
    - 1. Japan House #4 2. Japan House #5 3. Japan House #6, undated; ID: 122.0342 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0342)
      Duration: 50 minutes
    - 1. Japan House #7 2. Japan House #8 3. Satoru's Kitchen Concert #2 4. Satoru's Kitchen Concert #3, 1978; ID: 122.0343 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0343)
    - 1. Satoru at the Kitchen #4 2. Satoru at the Kitchen #5, 1978; ID: 122.0344 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0344)
      Duration: 45 minutes
    - 1. Heirlooms Act I - Intermission 2. Heirlooms Intermission - Act II, undated; ID: 122.0345 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0345)
    - 1. Heirlooms Act I Experiment 2. Heirlooms Act III Scene II 3. Heirlooms Act II Experiment, undated; ID: 122.0346 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0346)
    - 1. Heirlooms Act III Scene II - Experimental 2. Ghost Shot, undated, 1978; ID: 122.0347 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0347)
    - Document of Rehearsal at Cubicullo - a deux, 1974; ID: 122.0348 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0348)
    - Program, 1976; ID: 122.0349 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0349)
    - Program - entire dance, 1976; ID: 122.0350 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0350)
    - Program - Ward-Nasse Gallery, 1976; ID: 122.0351 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0351)
    - Spaces, 1973; ID: 122.0352 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0352)
    - 1. Wollman Hall Tape #2 2. Wollman Hall Tape #1 3. Wollman Hall Last Take, 1978; ID: 122.0353 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0353)
    - Wollman Hall Tape - Badly Recorded, 1978; ID: 122.0354 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0354)
    - 1. Wollman Hall Pan Spaces 2. Wollman Hall Pan From Elevator 3. Wall Section Tape #3, 1978; ID: 122.0355 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0355)
    - 1. Original Snow & Dances 2. Original Snow Shot 3. Snow Shot & Roof Section, undated, 1978; ID: 122.0356 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0356)
    - 1. Snow Shot, cont. 2. Tape Recorder Shot 3. Satoru Dancing Roof Section 4. Snow Shot, undated; ID: 122.0357 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0357)
    - Steven Backer's List of Dances, undated; ID: 122.0358 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0358)
    - 1. Steven Backer's List of Dances 2. Laura at Baruch College, undated; ID: 122.0359 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0359)
    - Laura at Baruch College & Rehearsal, undated; ID: 122.0360 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0360)
    - Dub of Parts of Laura Foreman's Performance, undated; ID: 122.0361 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0361)
    - 1. Dub of Parts of Laura Foreman's Performance 2. 127, undated; ID: 122.0362 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0362)
    - 1. Laura Foreman Interview 2. End of Women's Audition, 1978; ID: 122.0363 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0363)
    - 1. Lighting Part II 2. Women's Audition Part II 3. Men's Audition Beginning, 1978; ID: 122.0364 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0364)
    - 1. Men's Audition II 2. Men's Audition III, 1978; ID: 122.0365 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0365)
    - 1. Audition Callback Men & Women I 2. Audition Callback Men & Women II 3. Rehearsal #1, 1978; ID: 122.0366 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0366)
    - 1. Last Part of S & L in Loft 2. Loft Look Over 3. 5th Ave. Loft, undated; ID: 122.0367 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0367)
    - 1. S. Rehearsing and Misc. Shots 2. Lighting Discussion Continued, 1978, undated; ID: 122.0368 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0368)
    - 1. #141 Dub 2. #142 Dub, undated; ID: 122.0369 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0369)
    - 1. #143 Dub 2. #144 Dub, undated; ID: 122.0370 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0370)
    - 1. #145 Dub 2. #146 Dub, undated; ID: 122.0371 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0371)
    - 1. #147 Dub 2. #148 Dub, undated; ID: 122.0372 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0372)
    - a deux - Master Edit, 1977; ID: 122.0373 (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0373)
    - 1. #149 Dub 2. #150 Dub, undated; ID: 122.0374 (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0374)
    - 1. #150 Dub, cont 2. #151 Dub 3. #152 Dub 4. #153 Dub, undated; ID: 122.0375 (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0375)
    - 1. #153 Dub, cont 2. #154 Dub 3. #155 Dub, undated; ID: 122.0376 (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0376)
    - 1. #156 Dub 2. #157 Dub, undated; ID: 122.0377 (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0377)
    - 1. #158 Dub Poetry Reading 2. #159 Dub Poetry Reading 3. #160 Dub B. College, undated; ID: 122.0378 (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0378)
    - 1. #160 Dub, cont. 2. #161 Dub, undated; ID: 122.0379 (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0379)
    - 1. #162, Re-zeroed 2. #163, undated; ID: 122.0380 (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0380)